ANNA KHIZHNIAK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (VUE.JS)

CONTACT

- +380639596624
- Odessa / Bucharest
- Portfolio
- Telegram
- GitHub
- Linkedin

EDUCATION

2005 – 2009 COLLEGE OF INDUSTRIAL AUTOMATION ONAFT, ODESSA

Specialty: programmer for automated systems and EOM

2009 – 2013 SPECIALIST, ODESSA STATE ENVIRONMENTAL UNIVERSITY, ODESSA

Specialty: programmer

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SASS/SCSS
- JavaScript/Typescript
- React, Redux
- Vue.js, Vuex, Pinia
- GULP, Webpack
- Pug
- · GitHub, GitLab
- Node.js
- Bootstrap, Vuetify, Tailwind
- · Adaptive design
- Jest (basic knowledge)
- Express (basic knowledge)
- Mongo, Mongoose, SQLite (basic knowledge)
- Docker (basic knowledge)

PROFILE SUMMARY

I'm Front-end developer with commercial experience 6 month. I've been working with in HTML, CSS/SASS/SCSS, Javascript, Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, i18n.

I have technical degree, but I've been started my education in webdevelopment in 2021 and continue practicing through creating my own petprojects.

My knowledge is nothing without real practice, so I dream to get into a good team, multiply my experience and develop in programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer (Vue.js), WeStudy, remotely

MARCH - AUGUST 2024

- Work with RESTful API, JavaScript, Vue, Vuex, routing, i18n
- · Creating web-pages with custom components
- Work with mentor
- · Communication with command

Internship, remotely

JULY2023 — OCTOBER2023

- PUG
- React
- Javascript
- Adaptive design
- · Mentor support

Manager, content manager, copywriter, Online store, Odessa

2017 - 2023

- Add/edit/remove products on web-site
- · Add product description
- · Communication with suppliers,
- Mailing (with Mailchimp, Sendpulse),
- Work with clients (consulting, selling, orders, delivery control, resolve conficts)

Information support center operator, online technical support chat operator, Intertelecom, Odessa

 $2\,0\,1\,1\,-\,2\,0\,1\,7$

- Consulting clients (by phone and online)
- Interacting with other company departments for resolving client issues
- Selling company services

SOFT SKILLS

- Fast Learner
- Communication Skills
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Adaptability

LANGUAGES

- English: B1
- Ukrainian: Fluent

EDUCATION (COURSES)

Hillel "Front-end Pro" course, Odessa

AUGUST 2022 — FEBRUARY 2023

- · JavaScript,
- · React,
- Redux.
- GULP,
- · Webpack, OOP

Hillel "Front-end Basic" course, Odessa

MAY 2022 — AUGUST 2022

- HTML,
- CSS/SASS/SCSS,
- GULP

Hillel "Typescript" course, Odessa

NOVEMBER 2023 — FEBRUARY 2024

- Typescript,
- · Jest,
- · design patterns,
- · SOLID,
- OOP

Hillel "Node.js" course, Odessa

JANUARY2024 — APRIL2024

- Node.js,
- · Express,
- Mongo, Mongoose,
- · Docker,
- SQLite